[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 8 \u00d7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "49",
      "options": [
        "47",
        "54",
        "49",
        "51"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 10 + 8 \u00d7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "34",
      "options": [
        "34",
        "32",
        "39",
        "36"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 15 + 2 \u00d7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "23",
      "options": [
        "25",
        "23",
        "21",
        "28"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 15 + 1 \u00d7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "20",
      "options": [
        "22",
        "20",
        "18",
        "25"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 2 + 8 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "82",
      "options": [
        "82",
        "87",
        "80",
        "84"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 4 + 5 \u00d7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "14",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "19",
        "12",
        "16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 11 + 3 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "41",
      "options": [
        "39",
        "43",
        "41",
        "46"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 18 + 10 \u00d7 7?",
      "correctAnswer": "88",
      "options": [
        "88",
        "93",
        "90",
        "86"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 7 + 3 \u00d7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "22",
      "options": [
        "27",
        "24",
        "20",
        "22"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 1 + 1 \u00d7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "5",
      "options": [
        "7",
        "5",
        "10",
        "3"
      ]
    }
]